<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Javier Arriero OÜ</title>
    <link>https://javierarrieroou.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Javier Arriero OÜ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://javierarrieroou.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Clojure</title>
      <link>https://javierarrieroou.github.io/post/clojure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://javierarrieroou.github.io/post/clojure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Clojure is a dynamic, general-purpose programming language, combining the approachability and interactive development of a scripting language with an efficient and robust infrastructure for multithreaded programming. Clojure is a compiled language, yet remains completely dynamic – every feature supported by Clojure is supported at runtime. Clojure provides easy access to the Java frameworks, with optional type hints and type inference, to ensure that calls to Java can avoid reflection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clojure is a dialect of Lisp, and shares with Lisp the code-as-data philosophy and a powerful macro system. Clojure is predominantly a functional programming language, and features a rich set of immutable, persistent data structures. When mutable state is needed, Clojure offers a software transactional memory system and reactive Agent system that ensure clean, correct, multithreaded designs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teams external growing</title>
      <link>https://javierarrieroou.github.io/post/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://javierarrieroou.github.io/post/services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By growing externally, hiring outsourced developers into your team, you can dynamically grow your needs to achieve the development speed you need.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
